[
    {
        "front": "(かぜを)ひく",
        "back": "to catch (a cold)",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "のど",
        "back": "throat",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "せき",
        "back": "cough",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "ねつ",
        "back": "fever",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "れいぼう",
        "back": "air conditioning",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "だんぼう",
        "back": "heating",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "~まま",
        "back": "\"as is\", \"without changing\"",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "ねむる",
        "back": "to sleep",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "ねむい",
        "back": "sleepy",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "むり(する）",
        "back": "to exert oneself too; much",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "むりな",
        "back": "unreasonable; excessive",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "かたい",
        "back": "hard",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "やわらかい",
        "back": "soft",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "かむ",
        "back": "to bite",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "おれる",
        "back": "to break (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）おる",
        "back": "to break (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    },
    {
        "front": "はいしゃ",
        "back": "dentist",
        "chapter": "N4 C21"
    }
]